A Guide to the Clifton A. Woodrum Papers, 1979-1999
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Dated files, 1979-1999., Extent: 17.55 cu. ft. (39 boxes) (Box 96-123)
  - Subseries 2. 1980-1994, Extent: 3.15 cu. ft. (7 boxes)
    - 1982, [H.B. 603] Licensing for private security services. (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - 1982, [H.B. 772] Regulating real estate brokers. (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - 1982, [H.B. 914] Licensing fees for surplus lines insurance brokers. (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - 1982, [H.J.R. 107] Woodrum airfield extension. (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - 1983, Correspondence. (Box 100, Folder 18-24)
    - 1983, Report of the Attorney General Committee on Antitrust Immunity for Local Government. (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - 1983-1987, Virginia Democrats, New Faces. (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - 1984, Democratic Party of Virginia Convention. (Box 101, Folder 1-5)
    - 1984, Legislative agenda. (Box 101, Folder 6-9)
    - 1984, [H.B. 479] Coal slurry pipeline. (Box 101, Folder 10-16)
      Includes clippings, constituent correspondence, photographs, and reports regarding the debate over VEPCO's desire to install a coal slurry pipeline through Virginia.
    - 1984, [H.B. 479] Coal slurry pipeline. (Box 101a, Folder 1-13)
    - 1985, Budget. (Box 101a, Folder 14)
    - 1985, Index to budget. (Box 101a, Folder 15)
    - 1985, Handbook. (Box 101a, Folder 16)
    - 1985, Insurance. (Box 101a, Folder 17)
    - 1985, Misc. bills. (Box 101a, Folder 18)
    - 1986, Inaugural address of Gov. Baliles. (Box 101a, Folder 19)
    - 1986, [H.B. 2] Homestead exemption. (Box 101a, Folder 20)
    - 1986, [H.B. 3] Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act. (Box 101a, Folder 21)
    - 1986, [H.B. 53] Mandatory Training of Animal Wardens. (Box 101a, Folder 22)
    - 1986, [H.B. 54] Abandoned cemetery lots. (Box 101a, Folder 23)
    - 1986, [H.B. 78] Federal insurance for financial institutions. (Box 101a, Folder 24)
    - 1986, [H.B. 92] Medical malpractice review panels. (Box 101a, Folder 25)
    - 1986, [H.B. 93] Tort liability of hospitals. (Box 101a, Folder 26)
    - 1986, [H. B. 126] Fraudulent identification. (Box 101a, Folder 27)
    - 1986, [H.B. 129] Savings and Loans Associations. (Box 101b, Folder 1)
    - 1986, [H.B. 195] Statewide branching bill. (Box 101b, Folder 2)
    - 1986, [H.B. 285] Medical malpractice act definitions. (Box 101b, Folder 3)
    - 1986, [H.B. 395] Safety equipment in motor vehicles. (Box 101b, Folder 4)
    - 1986, [H.B. 482] Appeal bonds. (Box 101b, Folder 5)
    - 1986, [H.B. 486] Asbestos. (Box 101b, Folder 6-7)
    - 1986, [H.B. 489] Board and Department of Criminal Justice Services. (Box 101b, Folder 8)
    - 1986, [H.B. 512] Powers of cities and towns. (Box 101b, Folder 9)
    - 1986, [H.B. 513] Privacy Protection Act exemptions. (Box 101b, Folder 10)
    - 1986, [H.B. 854] Roanoke Regional Airport Commission. (Box 101b, Folder 11-12)
    - 1986, Session Summary. (Box 101b, Folder 13)
    - 1987, Special Session. (Box 101b, Folder 14)
    - 1987, Session. (Box 101b, Folder 15-18)
    - 1988, [H.B. 30] Budget. (Box 102, Folder 1-3)
    - 1989, Democratic Party of Virginia, Campaign Training Seminar. (Box 102, Folder 4-5)
    - 1989, Democratic Party of Virginia, Candidate Development Updates. (Box 102, Folder 6-8)
    - 1989, Democratic Party of Virginia, Democratic Perspective. (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - 1989, Democratic Party of Virginia, Candidate profiles. (Box 102, Folder 10-11)
    - 1990-1991, Roanoke Valley Merger, County Alliance for Regional Excellence. (Box 102, Folder 12-17)
    - 1994, [H.B. 642] Certification of Law Enforcement Officers. (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 3. 1995 Campaign and Election Files, Extent: 2.7 cu. ft. (6 boxes)
    - Campaign, General information, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Campaign, Announcement, 1995 May 9. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Campaign, Bills, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 3-4)
    - Campaign, City school convocation, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Campaign, Clippings, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Campaign, Commonwealth Sportsmen Alliance, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Campaign, Congratulation letters, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Campaign, Contributions, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Campaign, C. Richard Cranwell, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Campaign, Direct mail, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Campaign, Financial committee, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Campaign, Honeytree, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Campaign, Invitations to speak, 1995. (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Campaign, Juvenile crime, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Campaign, Landmark strategies, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Campaign, Letters to state employees and teachers, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Campaign, Meeting Darrel Baker, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Campaign, Memoranda, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Campaign, Miscellaneous, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Campaign, Newsletter, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Campaign, Roanoke Academy of Medicine Valley, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Campaign, Roanoke Times editorials, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Campaign, Statements, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Election, Advertising, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Election, Debates, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Election, Direct mail, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Election, Fundraising, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Election, Mail plan, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Election, Mailers, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 16-17)
    - Election, Notes, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Election, Phones, 1995. (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Election, Phone list 1995. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Election, Polling data 1995. (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Election, Press releases 1995. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Election, Walk sheets. (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - General, Correspondence A-L, 1995. (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - General, Correspondence M-Y, 1995. (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, 1995 March. (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, 1995 April. (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, 1995 May-June. (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, 1995 July-August. (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, 1995 September. (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, 1995 October. (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, 1995 November-December. (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, Statement, 1995 April 13. (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, Fundraiser, 1995. (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, To be written, 1995. (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, Donations 1995. (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - General, Correspondence Thank Yous, Donations 1995. (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - General, Blue Ridge Public TV, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - General, Correspondence- Boy Scouts, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - General, Campaign planning workbook, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - General, Greater Raleigh Court Civic League, 14 September 1995. (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - General, Health Care Forum, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - General, Friends of Chip Woodrum A-C, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - General, Friends of Chip Woodrum D-F, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - General, Friends of Chip Woodrum G-I, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - General, Friends of Chip Woodrum J-L, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - General, Friends of Chip Woodrum M-O, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - General, Friends of Chip Woodrum P-R, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - General, Friends of Chip Woodrum S-U, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - General, Friends of Chip Woodrum V-X,. (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - General, Guns in penitentiary, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - General, Law enforcement endorsement, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - General, Lottery profits, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - General, Newspaper articles, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - General, Presession material, 1995. (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - General, Prison funding, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - General, The Regional Chamber, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - General, Republican Party, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - General, Rotary Club, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - General, Senior News, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - General, 21st Senatorial precincts, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - General, Session summary, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 6a-6b)
    - General, Utilization Review Board, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - General, Virginia Governmental Employees Association, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - General, Virginia Institute of Political Leadership, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - General, Voter registration, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - General, WBRA, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - General, Workbook and session review, 1995. (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 4. 1996 Legislative Files, Extent: .90 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    - Summary of 1995 Budget actions to the 1994-1996 Budget, 1996. (Box 108, Folder volume)
    - 1995 Amendments to the 1994-1996 Appropriation Act, 1996. (Box 108, Folder volume)
    - 1996 Legislation, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - [H.B. 84] Roanoke Regional Airport, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - [H.B. 85] Crime History Checks, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - [H.B. 86] False police reports, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - [H.B. 88] Bodily Injury in Custody, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - [H.B. 89] Subsequent larceny, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - [H.B. 90] Emergency custody orders and temporary detention orders, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - [H.B. 220] Habitat for Humanity, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - [H.B. 221] City of Roanoke Charter, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - [H.B. 223] Home care tax credit, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - [H.B. 332] Involuntary commitment, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - [H.B. 335] Estate tax returns, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - [H.B. 338] Uniform Commercial Code, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - [H.B. 342] Real Estate Board, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - [H.B. 497] Gas utilities, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - [H.B. 498] Corporations and partners, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - [H.B. 499] Juvenile facilities, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - [H.B. 500] Sheriff fees, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - [H.B. 508] Interest on fines and costs, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - [H.B. 509] Committee on District Courts vacation, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - [H.B.] 510 Workers comp, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - [H.B. 754] FOIA Parole, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - [H.B. 755] Public Procurement Act, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - [H.B. 757] Insurance agents and consultants, 1996. (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 5. 1997 Election Files, Extent: .90 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    - Candidate packet. (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Chemical Manufacturing Association. (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Christian Coalition. (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Commendations. (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Commendations, 1995-1996. (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Contributors. (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Fundraiser, April 2007. (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Newsletter. (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Proposal. (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Public relations. (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Virginia for the Arts. (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Free. (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - League of Older Americans. (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Woodrum for House, Bank statements and deposits. (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Woodrum for House, Bank statements. (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Woodrum for House, Bills. (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Woodrum for House, Copies of checks. (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Woodrum for House, Copies of deposits. (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Woodrum for House, Fundraiser, 1998. (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Woodrum for House, Fundraiser, 1998. (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Woodrum for House, Fundraiser, 1998. (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 6. 1997 Legislative Files, Extent: 1.35 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
    - Anti-drug switching, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Center in the Square- Amendment provide funds for W. Va. Foundation for Arts, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Child custody, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - College of Health Sciences, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence- Miscellaneous, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence- Thank you, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Crime Commission, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Elk Hill Farm, Inc., 1997. (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Governor's school, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - I-73 Corridor Study, 1997. (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Mail response #1, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Mail response #2, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Mail response #3, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Mail no response, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Medical Society of Virginia HMO Accountability system, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Medicare for dentists, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Parental rights, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Radford University, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Regional Training Academies, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Roanoke County fingerprinting, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Benjamin Rush Political Action Committee, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - State song, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - State Librarian Salary, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Stranded chemist: ABC (Alcoholic Beverage Control) to DCJS (Dept. Criminal Justice Services), 1997. (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Summary of Budget Actions, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 14a)
    - Tent sales, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Tent sales, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Trees and outdoor signs, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Troopers from Commonwealth Attorney to Dept. of State Police, 1997. (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Center for Independent Living, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Crime Commission, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Education Association, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Girls State, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Virginia State Crime Commission Report, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 4a)
    - Virginia Vet Care Center, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Western Community College, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Water quality, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Woodrow Wilson Birthplace and Museum, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - H.B. 1567 Uniform Commercial Code, Article 6, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - [H.B. 1744] Sandra Kuehn relief, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - [H.B. 1811] Storage of biological evidence, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - [H.B. 1835] Purposes of Literary Loan Fund, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - [H.B. 1959] Physicians and administer of heroin, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - [H.B. 2000] Cemeteries, internment rights, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - [H.B. 2101] Public utilities rate experimentation, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - [H.B. 2102] Regional training academies, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - [H.B. 2249] Virginia Public Broadcasting Authority, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - [H.B. 2383] Architects: Good Samaritan, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - [H.B. 2384] Birth related neurological injury compensation program, Standards of care, fund assets, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - [H.B. 2390] BPOL: Day Care Center, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - [H.B. 2915] Rights of way, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 21)
    - [H.J.R. 402] Trial, appeal, and collateral proceedings of capital cases, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 22)
    - [H.J.R. 464] Study: Dept. of Corrections, policies and evaluation, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 23)
    - [H.J.R. 465] Study: Dept. of Corrections, staffing, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 24)
    - [H.J.R. 641] Study: Birth related neurological injury compensation program, increasing responsible use, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 25)
    - [H.J.R. 662] Literary fund monies, 1997. (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 7. 1998 Legislative Files, Extent: 2.25 cu. ft. (5 boxes)
    - Session summary, 1998. (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Index to session, 1998. (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Environmental voting summary, 1998. (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Special session, 1998. (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Chapter 464, 1998. (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Appellate oral argument, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - The House Democratic Caucus, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Constituent correspondence, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Constituent correspondence, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Constituent correspondence, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Constituent correspondence, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Constituent correspondence, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, District Court, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Early intervention, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1998. (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Crime commission, Hate crimes, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Fax files, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Freedom of Information Act drafts, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Misc. funding, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Hot Topics Legislation, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Law libraries, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Mental retardation, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Misc. co-patron legislation, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Moose lodges, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - No action, 1998. (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - No action, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Religious freedom, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - School Nurse Incentive Grants Program and Fund, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 4-6.03 #2h] VRS sheriff, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 20 #1h] Local Safety Alcohol Action Program, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 22 #1h] Election Transfer Protective Orders, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 29 #2h] Fee payments of indigent defense, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 30 #1h] General district court clerk's offices, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 31 #1h] Juvenile and domestic relations, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 32 #1h] Combined district court clerk's offices, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 33 #2h] Magistrates, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 84 #2h] Blue Ridge Public Television, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 129 #14h] Classroom Teacher skills for violence prevention, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 161 #3h] Community College technology fee, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 183 #9h] Virginia Tech, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 323 #1h] District Medical Examiners, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 333 #3h] Roanoke Redevelopment and Housing Authority, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 398 #2h] TAP parent training, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 433 #10h] Woodrow Wilson birthplace, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 449 #1h] Batterer intervention, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 455 #2h] Public inebriate services, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 455 #4h] Courts for drug involved offenders, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 455 #6h] Pre/post incarceration services, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 461 #1h] Internet web site, Sex offender registry, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 461 #4h] Expand sex offender registry, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 25)
    - [H.B. 30 Item 469 #2h] Field training for correction officers, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 26)
    - [H.B. 30 Item C-23 #1h and C-17.96 #1h] Virginia Western Community College, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 27)
    - [H.B. 32] Service upon corporations, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 28)
    - [H.B. 36], 1998. (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - [H.B. 38-40], 1998. (Box 117, Folder 30)
    - [H.B. 46] Tax funeral service providers, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 31)
    - [H.B. 59] Positive drug test as a disqualifier for commercial driver's license, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 32)
    - [H.B. 142] Prior service credit for certain members of the Virginia Retirement System, 1998. (Box 117, Folder 33)
    - [H.B. 155] Part time legislators, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - [H.B. 247] Relating to illegal drugs, definition of marijuana and penalty, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - [H.B. 322] Nonprofit organizations sales and use tax exemptions, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - [H.B. 331] Exemption of certain organizations from property taxes, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - [H.B. 332] Educational sales and use tax exemptions, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - [H.B. 486] Transport of bear and quail, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - [H.B. 565] Relating to insurance, insurer investment limits, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - [H.B. 566] Approval of compromises on behalf of persons under a disability, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - [H.B. 620] Discharges of oil, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - [H.B. 621] Batterer Intervention Certification and Monitoring Program, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - [H.B. 622] Filing of habeas corpus petitions in capital cases, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - [H.B. 808] Number of deputies, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - [H.B. 809] Board of Contractors, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - [H.B. 811] Firefighter grievance procedures, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - [H.B. 829] Indexing of deeds by tax map reference number, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - [H.B. 830] Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - [H.B. 864] Drugs by false pretenses, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - [H.B. 1204] Virginia Residential Property Disclosure Act, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - [H.B. 1205] Uniform Statewide Building Code definitions, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - [H.B. 1415] Board for Contractors requirements for licensure and exemption, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - [H.J.R. 86] TAP Total Action Against Poverty, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - [H.J.R. 106] Protection of human remains study, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - [H.J.R. 190] Capital representation for indigent defendants, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - [H.J.R. 285] Regional criminal justice academy training, 1998. (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 8. 1999 Legislative Files, Extent: 5.2 cu. ft. (12 boxes)
    - Final cumulative index, 1999. (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Session summary, 1999. (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Report of the Citizens' Advisory Committee on Legislative Compensation, 1999. (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Caucus, Session in Review, 1999. (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Guidelines for House of Delegates Interim Meetings, 1999. (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Rules of the House of Delegates, 1999. (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - CAW Legislation, 1999. (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 13 - 25 January 1999. (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 25 January - 5 February 1999. (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 5 - 7 February 1999. (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 8 - 12 February 1999. (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 13 - 27 February 1999. (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous. (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Crime Commission, 1999. (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Recommendations and Vetoes, 1999. (Box 121, Folder 2-3)
    - Judicial appointments, 1999. (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Medical malpractice, 1999. (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Misc. legislative issues, 1999. (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters, 1999. (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Teacher salaries, 1999. (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Commission on Family Violence Prevention, 1998-1999. (Box 121a)
    - [H.B. 540] Judicial Conference training, 1999. (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - [H.B. 721] Committee on Corporations, Insurance, and Banking, 1998-1999. (Box 121, Folder 10-11)
    - [H.B. 1450] Auditor Public Accounts (Item 17 #2h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 1)